today we're installing a 5.9 KW battery
a 3kw 24volt inverter and a 460 W panel
on this 1990 Toyota hyos the accessories
we're going to need for installation are
mc4 connectors insulated PV wire
mounting hardware solar entry Hood
bluetooth smart chunk connector tools
needed mc4 connector battery cable
crimper socket set and every man thing
located in this belt cuz if you ain't
get this type of [__] you shouldn't be
attempting this type of redneckery guys
first our mounting hardware one it and
obviously long enough you're going to
have to cut
it this one's got to be hurting
now need the saws on with a metal blade
to cut it
[Music]
safely these go together like
so tighten it on
down slides in there like so always
tighten them like that and then put that
Jang on it like this jst to apply
jankster
yeah hey John if I said put that jst on
it you know what I meant wouldn't you
jst jst janger put that janger on his
ass if you were tightening up both a
little extra
see yeah I know janky but janga J is the
word y'all just said it put that we we
on it see we we apply but then you put
that Jang on it like
do 38 Drive bit to fit these screws so
this panel's 40 41 in long so we're
going to go 45
[Music]
right you can kind of eyeball that can't
you how we looking right there go right
here right here always make sure you
going to hit something so drill
down yep hit something go ahead and
pilot that thing a little
bit turn it like that that way you can
fix it from the
outside that makes better sense don't it
T is there any way you see water can get
in there
joh it's secure to me now we need to put
some more down here don't wa to build it
up that right there probably level it
out don't you
think that thing in there too see how
it's blowed out the sides there ain't no
way water can get in
there that one here sounds a show show
slide it in there it up just a little
bit we ain't going to apply the jankster
to these yet not ready test 42 must
apply the jankster to all of it real
quick J Jank you know why it's called
the janger that's what it says listen J
you heard
that argue with it Cletus you can't
argue with a man putting solar panels on
a [__] Freedom wagon in flip
flops you cannot argue with me well you
could you be horribly [__]
wrong go
ahead I got it boy almost like he's
godamn made it to factory for this
[__] show them what you know
about size enough to breath it's just a
visual
here party
trick Dam Bob there we go we going
godamn fire going to bring our solar
wire down here got to be careful because
water collects in this belly I'm going
to drill this hole 9 in off the inside
wall where down inside the cabinet
behind this Plumbing
vent see right here I need one red and
one black I'm going to shoot this to
you you keep grabbing as much as you
need I just want to protect it inside
that cabinet through just like
that not going to tighten them down yet
email for the
positive I'm going to reach my positive
the little one goes in the big one got
my wire stripped
out not coming off it clicks it
fits click I got my wires crimped up
ready to clip in but it's obviously dark
as [__] so I'm going to come back
tomorrow finish up in the daylight and
post a whole F length video on YouTube
for the first time ever catch me in a
moment Cletus